[
    {
        "id": "words1 - 0",
        "front": "亦是",
        "back": "역시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 1",
        "front": "主義",
        "back": "주의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 2",
        "front": "工夫",
        "back": "공부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 3",
        "front": "個人",
        "back": "개인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 4",
        "front": "國家",
        "back": "국가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 5",
        "front": "競爭力",
        "back": "경쟁력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 6",
        "front": "單語",
        "back": "한자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 7",
        "front": "已往",
        "back": "이왕"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 8",
        "front": "吝嗇",
        "back": "인색"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 9",
        "front": "帽子",
        "back": "모자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 10",
        "front": "勿論",
        "back": "물론"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 11",
        "front": "甚至於",
        "back": "심지어"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 12",
        "front": "試驗",
        "back": "시험"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 13",
        "front": "互換",
        "back": "호환"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 14",
        "front": "沈沈",
        "back": "침침"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 15",
        "front": "酒煎子",
        "back": "주전자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 16",
        "front": "人稱代名詞",
        "back": "인칭대명사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 17",
        "front": "語助辭",
        "back": "어조사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 18",
        "front": "語彙",
        "back": "어휘"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 19",
        "front": "實感",
        "back": "실감"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 20",
        "front": "當然",
        "back": "당연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 21",
        "front": "別途",
        "back": "별도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 22",
        "front": "疑訝",
        "back": "의아"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 23",
        "front": "自由自在",
        "back": "자유자재"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 24",
        "front": "役割",
        "back": "역할"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 25",
        "front": "地域",
        "back": "지역"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 26",
        "front": "屬",
        "back": "속"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 27",
        "front": "關係",
        "back": "관계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 28",
        "front": "維持",
        "back": "유지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 29",
        "front": "亦是",
        "back": "역시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 30",
        "front": "主義",
        "back": "주의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 31",
        "front": "工夫",
        "back": "공부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 32",
        "front": "個人",
        "back": "개인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 33",
        "front": "國家",
        "back": "국가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 34",
        "front": "競爭力",
        "back": "경쟁력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 35",
        "front": "單語",
        "back": "한자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 36",
        "front": "已往",
        "back": "이왕"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 37",
        "front": "吝嗇",
        "back": "인색"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 38",
        "front": "帽子",
        "back": "모자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 39",
        "front": "勿論",
        "back": "물론"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 40",
        "front": "甚至於",
        "back": "심지어"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 41",
        "front": "試驗",
        "back": "시험"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 42",
        "front": "互換",
        "back": "호환"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 43",
        "front": "沈沈",
        "back": "침침"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 44",
        "front": "酒煎子",
        "back": "주전자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 45",
        "front": "人稱代名詞",
        "back": "인칭대명사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 46",
        "front": "語助辭",
        "back": "어조사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 47",
        "front": "語彙",
        "back": "어휘"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 48",
        "front": "實感",
        "back": "실감"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 49",
        "front": "當然",
        "back": "당연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 50",
        "front": "別途",
        "back": "별도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 51",
        "front": "疑訝",
        "back": "의아"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 52",
        "front": "自由自在",
        "back": "자유자재"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 53",
        "front": "役割",
        "back": "역할"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 54",
        "front": "地域",
        "back": "지역"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 55",
        "front": "屬",
        "back": "속"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 56",
        "front": "關係",
        "back": "관계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 57",
        "front": "維持",
        "back": "유지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 58",
        "front": "時人",
        "back": "시인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 59",
        "front": "任務",
        "back": "임무"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 60",
        "front": "實際",
        "back": "실제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 61",
        "front": "卽",
        "back": "즉"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 62",
        "front": "蓋然性",
        "back": "개연성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 63",
        "front": "必然性",
        "back": "필연성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 64",
        "front": "可能",
        "back": "가능"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 65",
        "front": "歷史家",
        "back": "역사가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 66",
        "front": "差異",
        "back": "차이"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 67",
        "front": "散文",
        "back": "산문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 68",
        "front": "韻文",
        "back": "운문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 69",
        "front": "韻律",
        "back": "운율"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 70",
        "front": "一種",
        "back": "일종"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 71",
        "front": "亦是",
        "back": "역시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 72",
        "front": "歷史",
        "back": "역사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 73",
        "front": "變",
        "back": "변"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 74",
        "front": "前者",
        "back": "전자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 75",
        "front": "後者",
        "back": "후자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 76",
        "front": "哲學的",
        "back": "철학적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 77",
        "front": "普遍的",
        "back": "보편적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 78",
        "front": "個別的",
        "back": "개별적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 79",
        "front": "特定",
        "back": "특정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 80",
        "front": "類型",
        "back": "유형"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 81",
        "front": "蓋然的",
        "back": "개연적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 82",
        "front": "必然的",
        "back": "필연적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 83",
        "front": "行",
        "back": "행"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 84",
        "front": "經驗",
        "back": "경험"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 85",
        "front": "意味",
        "back": "의미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 86",
        "front": "憂國",
        "back": "우국"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 87",
        "front": "願",
        "back": "원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 88",
        "front": "民族",
        "back": "민족"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 89",
        "front": "事業",
        "back": "사업"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 90",
        "front": "決",
        "back": "결"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 91",
        "front": "世界",
        "back": "세계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 92",
        "front": "武力",
        "back": "무력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 93",
        "front": "征服",
        "back": "정복"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 94",
        "front": "經濟力",
        "back": "경제력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 95",
        "front": "支配",
        "back": "지배"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 96",
        "front": "文化",
        "back": "문화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 97",
        "front": "平和",
        "back": "평화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 98",
        "front": "人類",
        "back": "인류"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 99",
        "front": "全體",
        "back": "전체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 100",
        "front": "義",
        "back": "의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 101",
        "front": "空想",
        "back": "공상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 102",
        "front": "者",
        "back": "자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 103",
        "front": "萬一",
        "back": "만일"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 104",
        "front": "石灰質",
        "back": "석회질"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 105",
        "front": "滿期",
        "back": "만기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 106",
        "front": "以前",
        "back": "이전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 107",
        "front": "聖潔",
        "back": "성결"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 108",
        "front": "精神",
        "back": "정신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 109",
        "front": "決心",
        "back": "결심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 110",
        "front": "標",
        "back": "표"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 111",
        "front": "名",
        "back": "명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 112",
        "front": "九",
        "back": "구"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 113",
        "front": "號",
        "back": "호"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 114",
        "front": "白凡",
        "back": "백범"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 115",
        "front": "同志",
        "back": "동지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 116",
        "front": "言布",
        "back": "언포"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 117",
        "front": "龜",
        "back": "귀"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 118",
        "front": "改",
        "back": "개"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 119",
        "front": "倭",
        "back": "왜"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 120",
        "front": "民籍",
        "back": "민적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 121",
        "front": "蓮下",
        "back": "연하"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 122",
        "front": "監獄",
        "back": "감옥"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 123",
        "front": "多年",
        "back": "다년"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 124",
        "front": "硏究",
        "back": "연구"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 125",
        "front": "依",
        "back": "의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 126",
        "front": "下等",
        "back": "하등"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 127",
        "front": "社會",
        "back": "사회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 128",
        "front": "白丁",
        "back": "백정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 129",
        "front": "凡夫",
        "back": "범부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 130",
        "front": "愛國心",
        "back": "애국심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 131",
        "front": "現今",
        "back": "현금"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 132",
        "front": "程度",
        "back": "정도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 133",
        "front": "完全",
        "back": "완전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 134",
        "front": "獨立",
        "back": "독립"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 135",
        "front": "民國",
        "back": "민국"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 136",
        "front": "願望",
        "back": "원망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 137",
        "front": "服役",
        "back": "복역"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 138",
        "front": "琉璃廠",
        "back": "유리창"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 139",
        "front": "政府",
        "back": "정부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 140",
        "front": "建設",
        "back": "건설"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 141",
        "front": "窓戶",
        "back": "창호"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 142",
        "front": "本姓",
        "back": "본성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 143",
        "front": "要素",
        "back": "요소"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 144",
        "front": "番",
        "back": "번"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 145",
        "front": "競爭心",
        "back": "경쟁심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 146",
        "front": "小心",
        "back": "소심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 147",
        "front": "名譽慾",
        "back": "명예욕"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 148",
        "front": "利得",
        "back": "이득"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 149",
        "front": "爲",
        "back": "위"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 150",
        "front": "安全",
        "back": "안전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 151",
        "front": "保障",
        "back": "보장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 152",
        "front": "評判",
        "back": "평판"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 153",
        "front": "害",
        "back": "해"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 154",
        "front": "誘導",
        "back": "유도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 155",
        "front": "妻",
        "back": "처"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 156",
        "front": "子息",
        "back": "자식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 157",
        "front": "家畜",
        "back": "가축"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 158",
        "front": "自己",
        "back": "자기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 159",
        "front": "保護",
        "back": "보호"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 160",
        "front": "防禦",
        "back": "방어"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 161",
        "front": "直接的",
        "back": "직접적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 162",
        "front": "間接的",
        "back": "간접적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 163",
        "front": "相異",
        "back": "상이"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 164",
        "front": "同僚",
        "back": "동료"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 165",
        "front": "職業",
        "back": "직업"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 166",
        "front": "暴力",
        "back": "폭력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 167",
        "front": "使用",
        "back": "사용"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 168",
        "front": "等",
        "back": "등"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 169",
        "front": "强力",
        "back": "강력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 170",
        "front": "狀況",
        "back": "상황"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 171",
        "front": "狀態",
        "back": "상태"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 172",
        "front": "分明",
        "back": "분명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 173",
        "front": "萬人",
        "back": "만인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 174",
        "front": "對",
        "back": "대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 175",
        "front": "戰爭",
        "back": "전쟁"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 176",
        "front": "結果",
        "back": "결과"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 177",
        "front": "結實",
        "back": "결실"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 178",
        "front": "勞動",
        "back": "노동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 179",
        "front": "土地",
        "back": "토지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 180",
        "front": "航海",
        "back": "항해"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 181",
        "front": "不確實性",
        "back": "불확실성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 182",
        "front": "支配",
        "back": "지배"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 183",
        "front": "意味",
        "back": "의미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 184",
        "front": "理由",
        "back": "이유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 185",
        "front": "輸入",
        "back": "수입"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 186",
        "front": "價値",
        "back": "가치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 187",
        "front": "建物",
        "back": "건물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 188",
        "front": "物件",
        "back": "물건"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 189",
        "front": "移動",
        "back": "이동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 190",
        "front": "運送",
        "back": "운송"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 191",
        "front": "手段",
        "back": "수단"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 192",
        "front": "地球",
        "back": "지구"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 193",
        "front": "知識",
        "back": "지식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 194",
        "front": "計算",
        "back": "계산"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 195",
        "front": "藝術",
        "back": "예술"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 196",
        "front": "文學",
        "back": "문학"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 197",
        "front": "社會",
        "back": "사회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 198",
        "front": "存在",
        "back": "존재"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 199",
        "front": "恐怖感",
        "back": "공포감"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 200",
        "front": "孤立",
        "back": "고립"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 201",
        "front": "悲慘",
        "back": "비참"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 202",
        "front": "短命",
        "back": "단명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 203",
        "front": "危險性",
        "back": "위험성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 204",
        "front": "登場",
        "back": "등장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 205",
        "front": "險惡",
        "back": "험악"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 206",
        "front": "天性的",
        "back": "천성적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 207",
        "front": "制約",
        "back": "제약"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 208",
        "front": "拘束",
        "back": "구속"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 209",
        "front": "統制",
        "back": "통제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 210",
        "front": "加",
        "back": "가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 211",
        "front": "同意",
        "back": "동의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 212",
        "front": "窮極的",
        "back": "궁극적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 213",
        "front": "原因",
        "back": "원인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 214",
        "front": "動機",
        "back": "동기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 215",
        "front": "生命",
        "back": "생명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 216",
        "front": "自身",
        "back": "자신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 217",
        "front": "保存",
        "back": "보존"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 218",
        "front": "結果",
        "back": "결과"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 219",
        "front": "滿足",
        "back": "만족"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 220",
        "front": "洞察",
        "back": "통찰 力 력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 221",
        "front": "君臨",
        "back": "군림"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 222",
        "front": "處罰",
        "back": "처벌"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 223",
        "front": "可視的",
        "back": "가시적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 224",
        "front": "勸力",
        "back": "권력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 225",
        "front": "自然",
        "back": "자연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 226",
        "front": "慾求",
        "back": "욕구"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 227",
        "front": "熱望",
        "back": "열망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 228",
        "front": "悽慘",
        "back": "처참"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 229",
        "front": "拘束",
        "back": "구속"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 230",
        "front": "集團",
        "back": "집단"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 231",
        "front": "讓渡",
        "back": "양도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 232",
        "front": "意志",
        "back": "의지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 233",
        "front": "多數決",
        "back": "다수결"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 234",
        "front": "縮小",
        "back": "축소"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 235",
        "front": "代替",
        "back": "대체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 236",
        "front": "落木寒天",
        "back": "낙목한천"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 237",
        "front": "瘦石",
        "back": "수석"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 238",
        "front": "妙境",
        "back": "묘경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 239",
        "front": "東洋",
        "back": "동양"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 240",
        "front": "畵宣紙",
        "back": "화선지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 241",
        "front": "省略",
        "back": "생략"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 242",
        "front": "抽象",
        "back": "추상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 243",
        "front": "氣骨",
        "back": "기골"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 244",
        "front": "능然",
        "back": "연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 245",
        "front": "物體",
        "back": "물체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 246",
        "front": "石壽圖",
        "back": "석수도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 247",
        "front": "無味",
        "back": "무미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 248",
        "front": "最上",
        "back": "최상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 249",
        "front": "味",
        "back": "미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 250",
        "front": "寂然不動",
        "back": "적연부동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 251",
        "front": "雷聲霹靂",
        "back": "뇌성벽력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 252",
        "front": "美學",
        "back": "미학"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 253",
        "front": "通",
        "back": "통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 254",
        "front": "水墨畵",
        "back": "수묵화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 255",
        "front": "精神",
        "back": "정신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 256",
        "front": "寫實",
        "back": "사실"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 257",
        "front": "芭蕉",
        "back": "파초"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 258",
        "front": "白雪",
        "back": "백설"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 259",
        "front": "十里",
        "back": "십리"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 260",
        "front": "山水",
        "back": "산수"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 261",
        "front": "風景",
        "back": "풍경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 262",
        "front": "畫幅",
        "back": "화폭"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 263",
        "front": "微笑",
        "back": "미소"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 264",
        "front": "畫境",
        "back": "화경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 265",
        "front": "事實",
        "back": "사실"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 266",
        "front": "四君子",
        "back": "사군자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 267",
        "front": "書藝",
        "back": "서예"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 268",
        "front": "抽象",
        "back": "추상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 269",
        "front": "派",
        "back": "파"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 270",
        "front": "畫家",
        "back": "화가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 271",
        "front": "模樣",
        "back": "모양"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 272",
        "front": "當然",
        "back": "당연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 273",
        "front": "趨勢",
        "back": "추세"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 274",
        "front": "價値",
        "back": "가치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 275",
        "front": "基準",
        "back": "기준"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 276",
        "front": "本質的",
        "back": "본질적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 277",
        "front": "生命感",
        "back": "생명감"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 278",
        "front": "無限",
        "back": "무한"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 279",
        "front": "波動",
        "back": "파동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 280",
        "front": "永遠",
        "back": "영원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 281",
        "front": "美",
        "back": "미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 282",
        "front": "謁見",
        "back": "알현"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 283",
        "front": "渴症",
        "back": "갈증"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 284",
        "front": "享有",
        "back": "향유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 285",
        "front": "侮辱",
        "back": "모욕"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 286",
        "front": "搜所聞",
        "back": "수소문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 287",
        "front": "說明",
        "back": "설명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 288",
        "front": "喜悅",
        "back": "희열"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 289",
        "front": "大陸",
        "back": "대륙"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 290",
        "front": "緣由",
        "back": "연유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 291",
        "front": "神話",
        "back": "신화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 292",
        "front": "登場",
        "back": "등장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 293",
        "front": "始作",
        "back": "시작"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 294",
        "front": "沿岸",
        "back": "연안"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 295",
        "front": "散步",
        "back": "산보"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 296",
        "front": "最初",
        "back": "최초"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 297",
        "front": "後代",
        "back": "후대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 298",
        "front": "英雄",
        "back": "영웅"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 299",
        "front": "相當數",
        "back": "상당수"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 300",
        "front": "子孫",
        "back": "자손"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 301",
        "front": "程度",
        "back": "정도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 302",
        "front": "外道",
        "back": "외도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 303",
        "front": "宮闕",
        "back": "궁궐"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 304",
        "front": "世上",
        "back": "세상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 305",
        "front": "處女",
        "back": "처녀"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 306",
        "front": "距離",
        "back": "거리"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 307",
        "front": "視力",
        "back": "시력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 308",
        "front": "婦人",
        "back": "부인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 309",
        "front": "變身",
        "back": "변신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 310",
        "front": "接近",
        "back": "접근"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 311",
        "front": "近處",
        "back": "근처"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 312",
        "front": "貴",
        "back": "귀"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 313",
        "front": "自己",
        "back": "자기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 314",
        "front": "海邊",
        "back": "해변"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 315",
        "front": "猛烈",
        "back": "맹렬"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 316",
        "front": "結局",
        "back": "결국"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 317",
        "front": "波濤",
        "back": "파도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 318",
        "front": "突進",
        "back": "돌진"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 319",
        "front": "必死的",
        "back": "필사적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 320",
        "front": "只今",
        "back": "지금"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 321",
        "front": "地名",
        "back": "지명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 322",
        "front": "傳說",
        "back": "전설"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 323",
        "front": "實際",
        "back": "실제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 324",
        "front": "紀元前",
        "back": "기원전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 325",
        "front": "世紀",
        "back": "세기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 326",
        "front": "作品",
        "back": "작품"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 327",
        "front": "歷史家",
        "back": "역사가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 328",
        "front": "理由",
        "back": "이유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 329",
        "front": "唯一",
        "back": "유일"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 330",
        "front": "起源",
        "back": "기원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 331",
        "front": "說",
        "back": "설"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 332",
        "front": "破竹之勢",
        "back": "파죽지세"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 333",
        "front": "累卵之危",
        "back": "누란지위"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 334",
        "front": "亡羊之歎",
        "back": "망양지탄"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 335",
        "front": "刻骨難忘",
        "back": "각골난망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 336",
        "front": "妻",
        "back": "아내 처"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 337",
        "front": "泳",
        "back": "헤엄 영"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 338",
        "front": "永",
        "back": "영원 영"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 339",
        "front": "速度",
        "back": "속도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 340",
        "front": "爲",
        "back": "위"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 341",
        "front": "隣接",
        "back": "인접"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 342",
        "front": "設置",
        "back": "설치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 343",
        "front": "駐車場",
        "back": "주차장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 344",
        "front": "顧客",
        "back": "고객"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 345",
        "front": "計算",
        "back": "계산"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 346",
        "front": "臺",
        "back": "대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 347",
        "front": "飮食",
        "back": "음식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 348",
        "front": "大體",
        "back": "대체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 349",
        "front": "注文",
        "back": "주문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 350",
        "front": "傳達",
        "back": "전달"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 351",
        "front": "食堂",
        "back": "식당"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 352",
        "front": "多樣",
        "back": "다양"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 353",
        "front": "選擇",
        "back": "선택"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 354",
        "front": "對照",
        "back": "대조"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 355",
        "front": "食卓",
        "back": "식탁"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 356",
        "front": "食事",
        "back": "식사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 357",
        "front": "餘地",
        "back": "여지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 358",
        "front": "休紙",
        "back": "휴지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 359",
        "front": "桶",
        "back": "통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 360",
        "front": "自動車",
        "back": "자동차"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 361",
        "front": "活動",
        "back": "활동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 362",
        "front": "大槪",
        "back": "대개"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 363",
        "front": "境遇",
        "back": "경우"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 364",
        "front": "化",
        "back": "화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 365",
        "front": "場所",
        "back": "장소"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 366",
        "front": "移動",
        "back": "이동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 367",
        "front": "近來",
        "back": "근래"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 368",
        "front": "店",
        "back": "점"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 369",
        "front": "經營者",
        "back": "경영자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 370",
        "front": "過程",
        "back": "과정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 371",
        "front": "運轉",
        "back": "운전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 372",
        "front": "者",
        "back": "자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 373",
        "front": "發見",
        "back": "발견"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 374",
        "front": "效率的",
        "back": "효율적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 375",
        "front": "窓口",
        "back": "창구"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 376",
        "front": "設置",
        "back": "설치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 377",
        "front": "全體",
        "back": "전체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 378",
        "front": "店鋪",
        "back": "점포"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 379",
        "front": "折半",
        "back": "절반"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 380",
        "front": "程度",
        "back": "정도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 381",
        "front": "駐車",
        "back": "주차"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 382",
        "front": "非效率的",
        "back": "비효율적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 383",
        "front": "代身",
        "back": "대신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 384",
        "front": "目的地",
        "back": "목적지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 385",
        "front": "向",
        "back": "향"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 386",
        "front": "立場",
        "back": "입장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 387",
        "front": "利用",
        "back": "이용"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 388",
        "front": "空間",
        "back": "공간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 389",
        "front": "從業員",
        "back": "종업원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 390",
        "front": "必要性",
        "back": "필요성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 391",
        "front": "別途",
        "back": "별도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 392",
        "front": "定期的",
        "back": "정기적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 393",
        "front": "雇用",
        "back": "고용"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 394",
        "front": "必要",
        "back": "필요"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 395",
        "front": "歷史",
        "back": "역사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 396",
        "front": "傳統",
        "back": "전통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 397",
        "front": "前文",
        "back": "전문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 398",
        "front": "建立",
        "back": "건립"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 399",
        "front": "臨時",
        "back": "임시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 400",
        "front": "政府",
        "back": "정부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 401",
        "front": "法統",
        "back": "법통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 402",
        "front": "不義",
        "back": "불의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 403",
        "front": "抗拒",
        "back": "항거"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 404",
        "front": "民主",
        "back": "민주"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 405",
        "front": "理念",
        "back": "이념"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 406",
        "front": "繼承",
        "back": "계승"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 407",
        "front": "祖國",
        "back": "조국"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 408",
        "front": "改革",
        "back": "개혁"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 409",
        "front": "平和的",
        "back": "평화적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 410",
        "front": "統一",
        "back": "통일"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 411",
        "front": "使命",
        "back": "사명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 412",
        "front": "立脚",
        "back": "입각"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 413",
        "front": "同胞愛",
        "back": "동포애"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 414",
        "front": "民族",
        "back": "민족"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 415",
        "front": "團結",
        "back": "단결"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 416",
        "front": "社會的",
        "back": "사회적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 417",
        "front": "弊習",
        "back": "폐습"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 418",
        "front": "打破",
        "back": "타파"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 419",
        "front": "自律",
        "back": "자율"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 420",
        "front": "調和",
        "back": "조화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 421",
        "front": "基本",
        "back": "기본"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 422",
        "front": "秩序",
        "back": "질서"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 423",
        "front": "確固",
        "back": "확고"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 424",
        "front": "政治",
        "back": "정치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 425",
        "front": "經濟",
        "back": "경제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 426",
        "front": "社會",
        "back": "사회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 427",
        "front": "文化",
        "back": "문화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 428",
        "front": "領域",
        "back": "영역"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 429",
        "front": "各人",
        "back": "각인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 430",
        "front": "機會",
        "back": "기회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 431",
        "front": "均等",
        "back": "균등"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 432",
        "front": "能力",
        "back": "능력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 433",
        "front": "最高度",
        "back": "최고도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 434",
        "front": "發揮",
        "back": "발휘"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 435",
        "front": "自由",
        "back": "자유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 436",
        "front": "權利",
        "back": "권리"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 437",
        "front": "責任",
        "back": "책임"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 438",
        "front": "義務",
        "back": "의무"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 439",
        "front": "完遂",
        "back": "완수"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 440",
        "front": "均等",
        "back": "균등"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 441",
        "front": "向上",
        "back": "향상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 442",
        "front": "企",
        "back": "기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 443",
        "front": "恒久的",
        "back": "항구적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 444",
        "front": "人類",
        "back": "인류"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 445",
        "front": "共營",
        "back": "공영"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 446",
        "front": "平和",
        "back": "평화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 447",
        "front": "子孫",
        "back": "자손"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 448",
        "front": "安全",
        "back": "안전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 449",
        "front": "幸福",
        "back": "행복"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 450",
        "front": "永遠",
        "back": "영원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 451",
        "front": "制定",
        "back": "제정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 452",
        "front": "改正",
        "back": "개정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 453",
        "front": "憲法",
        "back": "헌법"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 454",
        "front": "國會",
        "back": "국회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 455",
        "front": "議決",
        "back": "의결"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 456",
        "front": "國民投票",
        "back": "국민투표"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 457",
        "front": "依",
        "back": "의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 458",
        "front": "挑發",
        "back": "도발"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 459",
        "front": "逃亡",
        "back": "도망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 460",
        "front": "跳",
        "back": "도약 도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 461",
        "front": "努力",
        "back": "노력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 462",
        "front": "憤怒",
        "back": "분노"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 463",
        "front": "賣國奴",
        "back": "매국노"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 464",
        "front": "勞動",
        "back": "노동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 465",
        "front": "連絡",
        "back": "연락"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 466",
        "front": "春夏秋冬",
        "back": "춘하추동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 467",
        "front": "終日",
        "back": "종일"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 468",
        "front": "等級",
        "back": "등급"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 469",
        "front": "供給",
        "back": "공급"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 470",
        "front": "梅實",
        "back": "매실"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 471",
        "front": "蘭草",
        "back": "난초"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 472",
        "front": "竹林",
        "back": "죽림"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 473",
        "front": "傳統",
        "back": "전통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 474",
        "front": "美",
        "back": "미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 475",
        "front": "親",
        "back": "친"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 476",
        "front": "環境",
        "back": "환경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 477",
        "front": "性",
        "back": "성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 478",
        "front": "强調",
        "back": "강조"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 479",
        "front": "天然",
        "back": "천연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 480",
        "front": "染色",
        "back": "염색"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 481",
        "front": "對",
        "back": "대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 482",
        "front": "關心",
        "back": "관심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 483",
        "front": "職場",
        "back": "직장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 484",
        "front": "家庭",
        "back": "가정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 485",
        "front": "黃土",
        "back": "황토"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 486",
        "front": "流行",
        "back": "유행"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 487",
        "front": "歷代",
        "back": "역대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 488",
        "front": "令夫人",
        "back": "영부인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 489",
        "front": "技法",
        "back": "기법"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 490",
        "front": "優雅",
        "back": "우아"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 491",
        "front": "洗練",
        "back": "세련"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 492",
        "front": "演出",
        "back": "연출"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 493",
        "front": "百貨店",
        "back": "백화점"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 494",
        "front": "文化",
        "back": "문화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 495",
        "front": "開設",
        "back": "개설"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 496",
        "front": "講座",
        "back": "강좌"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 497",
        "front": "一般人",
        "back": "일반인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 498",
        "front": "熱狂",
        "back": "열광"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 499",
        "front": "自然",
        "back": "자연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 500",
        "front": "染料",
        "back": "염료"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 501",
        "front": "纖維",
        "back": "섬유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 502",
        "front": "色",
        "back": "색"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 503",
        "front": "採取",
        "back": "채취"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 504",
        "front": "源",
        "back": "원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 505",
        "front": "動物",
        "back": "동물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 506",
        "front": "鑛物",
        "back": "광물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 507",
        "front": "植物",
        "back": "식물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 508",
        "front": "先祖",
        "back": "선조"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 509",
        "front": "愛用",
        "back": "애용"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 510",
        "front": "普通",
        "back": "보통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 511",
        "front": "種類",
        "back": "종류"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 512",
        "front": "採取",
        "back": "채취"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 513",
        "front": "量",
        "back": "량"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 514",
        "front": "限定",
        "back": "한정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 515",
        "front": "分泌物",
        "back": "분비물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 516",
        "front": "色素",
        "back": "색소"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 517",
        "front": "草創期",
        "back": "초창기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 518",
        "front": "主",
        "back": "주"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 519",
        "front": "使用",
        "back": "사용"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 520",
        "front": "反",
        "back": "반"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 521",
        "front": "心材",
        "back": "심재"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 522",
        "front": "等",
        "back": "등"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 523",
        "front": "豐富",
        "back": "풍부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 524",
        "front": "發達",
        "back": "발달"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 525",
        "front": "單色",
        "back": "단색"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 526",
        "front": "多色",
        "back": "다색"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 527",
        "front": "抽出",
        "back": "추출"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 528",
        "front": "時間",
        "back": "시간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 529",
        "front": "過程",
        "back": "과정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 530",
        "front": "複雜",
        "back": "복잡"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 531",
        "front": "材料",
        "back": "재료"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 532",
        "front": "産地",
        "back": "산지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 533",
        "front": "採取",
        "back": "채취"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 534",
        "front": "時期",
        "back": "시기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 535",
        "front": "保管",
        "back": "보관"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 536",
        "front": "狀態",
        "back": "상태"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 537",
        "front": "合成",
        "back": "합성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 538",
        "front": "模倣",
        "back": "모방"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 539",
        "front": "美麗",
        "back": "미려"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 540",
        "front": "色彩",
        "back": "색채"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 541",
        "front": "明度",
        "back": "명도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 542",
        "front": "中間",
        "back": "중간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 543",
        "front": "彩度",
        "back": "채도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 544",
        "front": "表現",
        "back": "표현"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 545",
        "front": "便安",
        "back": "편안"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 546",
        "front": "人體",
        "back": "인체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 547",
        "front": "有害",
        "back": "유해"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 548",
        "front": "公害",
        "back": "공해"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 549",
        "front": "物質",
        "back": "물질"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 550",
        "front": "尺度",
        "back": "척도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 551",
        "front": "只今",
        "back": "지금"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 552",
        "front": "乃至",
        "back": "내지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 553",
        "front": "斤",
        "back": "도끼 근"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 554",
        "front": "折半",
        "back": "절반"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 555",
        "front": "分析",
        "back": "분석"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 556",
        "front": "排斥",
        "back": "배척"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 557",
        "front": "炎症",
        "back": "염증"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 558",
        "front": "徹頭徹尾",
        "back": "철두철미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 559",
        "front": "音",
        "back": "음"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 560",
        "front": "員",
        "back": "원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 561",
        "front": "淡淡",
        "back": "담담"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 562",
        "front": "粉末",
        "back": "분말"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 563",
        "front": "憤怒",
        "back": "분노"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 564",
        "front": "咸興",
        "back": "함흥"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 565",
        "front": "一片丹心",
        "back": "일편단심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 566",
        "front": "天安",
        "back": "천안"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 567",
        "front": "艦",
        "back": "함"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 568",
        "front": "鑑賞",
        "back": "감상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 569",
        "front": "濫用",
        "back": "남용"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 570",
        "front": "監視",
        "back": "감시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 571",
        "front": "時代",
        "back": "시대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 572",
        "front": "不問",
        "back": "불문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 573",
        "front": "人間",
        "back": "인간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 574",
        "front": "理想的",
        "back": "이상적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 575",
        "front": "肉體",
        "back": "육체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 576",
        "front": "關心",
        "back": "관심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 577",
        "front": "美術家",
        "back": "미술가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 578",
        "front": "作品",
        "back": "작품"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 579",
        "front": "彫刻家",
        "back": "조각가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 580",
        "front": "主題",
        "back": "주제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 581",
        "front": "女體",
        "back": "여체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 582",
        "front": "豐滿",
        "back": "풍만"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 583",
        "front": "本格的",
        "back": "본격적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 584",
        "front": "始作",
        "back": "시작"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 585",
        "front": "當代",
        "back": "당대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 586",
        "front": "最高",
        "back": "최고"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 587",
        "front": "巨匠",
        "back": "거장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 588",
        "front": "亦是",
        "back": "역시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 589",
        "front": "特",
        "back": "특"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 590",
        "front": "基準",
        "back": "기준"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 591",
        "front": "比例",
        "back": "비례"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 592",
        "front": "數學的",
        "back": "수학적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 593",
        "front": "甚",
        "back": "심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 594",
        "front": "程度",
        "back": "정도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 595",
        "front": "印象派",
        "back": "인상파"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 596",
        "front": "畫家",
        "back": "화가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 597",
        "front": "關",
        "back": "관"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 598",
        "front": "證言",
        "back": "증언"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 599",
        "front": "者",
        "back": "자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 600",
        "front": "以來",
        "back": "이래"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 601",
        "front": "歲月",
        "back": "세월"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 602",
        "front": "專門家",
        "back": "전문가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 603",
        "front": "西洋",
        "back": "서양"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 604",
        "front": "健康",
        "back": "건강"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 605",
        "front": "均衡",
        "back": "균형"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 606",
        "front": "追求",
        "back": "추구"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 607",
        "front": "願",
        "back": "원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 608",
        "front": "惟獨",
        "back": "유독"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 609",
        "front": "世紀",
        "back": "세기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 610",
        "front": "待接",
        "back": "대접"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 611",
        "front": "自身",
        "back": "자신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 612",
        "front": "能力",
        "back": "능력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 613",
        "front": "體力",
        "back": "체력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 614",
        "front": "運動量",
        "back": "운동량"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 615",
        "front": "調節",
        "back": "조절"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 616",
        "front": "家庭",
        "back": "가정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 617",
        "front": "野外",
        "back": "야외"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 618",
        "front": "危險性",
        "back": "위험성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 619",
        "front": "運動",
        "back": "운동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 620",
        "front": "安心",
        "back": "안심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 621",
        "front": "若干",
        "back": "약간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 622",
        "front": "訓練",
        "back": "훈련"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 623",
        "front": "通",
        "back": "통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 624",
        "front": "基本",
        "back": "기본"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 625",
        "front": "技",
        "back": "기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 626",
        "front": "家族",
        "back": "가족"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 627",
        "front": "空間",
        "back": "공간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 628",
        "front": "複雜",
        "back": "복잡"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 629",
        "front": "器具",
        "back": "기구"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 630",
        "front": "等",
        "back": "등"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 631",
        "front": "必要",
        "back": "필요"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 632",
        "front": "長點",
        "back": "장점"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 633",
        "front": "動作",
        "back": "동작"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 634",
        "front": "要求",
        "back": "요구"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 635",
        "front": "特性",
        "back": "특성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 636",
        "front": "上",
        "back": "상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 637",
        "front": "短期",
        "back": "단기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 638",
        "front": "間",
        "back": "간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 639",
        "front": "行動",
        "back": "행동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 640",
        "front": "敏捷",
        "back": "민첩"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 641",
        "front": "性",
        "back": "성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 642",
        "front": "集中力",
        "back": "집중력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 643",
        "front": "向上",
        "back": "향상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 644",
        "front": "實際",
        "back": "실제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 645",
        "front": "時速",
        "back": "시속"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 646",
        "front": "跳躍",
        "back": "도약"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 647",
        "front": "回傳",
        "back": "회전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 648",
        "front": "全身運動",
        "back": "전신운동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 649",
        "front": "神經系",
        "back": "신경계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 650",
        "front": "勿論",
        "back": "물론"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 651",
        "front": "呼吸",
        "back": "호흡"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 652",
        "front": "循環系",
        "back": "순환계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 653",
        "front": "發達",
        "back": "발달"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 654",
        "front": "活動",
        "back": "활동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 655",
        "front": "形態",
        "back": "형태"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 656",
        "front": "現代",
        "back": "현대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 657",
        "front": "人",
        "back": "인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 658",
        "front": "發生",
        "back": "발생"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 659",
        "front": "因",
        "back": "인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 660",
        "front": "胃腸",
        "back": "위장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 661",
        "front": "障碍",
        "back": "장애"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 662",
        "front": "效果的",
        "back": "효과적"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 663",
        "front": "相對",
        "back": "상대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 664",
        "front": "親睦",
        "back": "친목"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 665",
        "front": "圓滿",
        "back": "원만"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 666",
        "front": "對人關係",
        "back": "대인관계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words1 - 667",
        "front": "形成",
        "back": "형성"
    }
]